Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Spain (1955-1961) File, 1944-1961 (Boxes 85-117)
  - Correspondence, 1944-1961
    - Lodge, Henry Sears, 1957 (Box-folder 104: 6)
    - Lodge, Lily, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 104: 7)
    - Lodge, Mary, 1961 (Box-folder 104: 8)
    - Lodge, Matilda Elizabeth, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 104: 9)
    - Logan, John, 1960 (Box-folder 104: 10)
    - Loomis, Mrs. A. Hubble, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 104: 11)
    - Louveau, Simone, 1955 (Box-folder 104: 12)
    - Luce, Mr. and Mrs. Henry, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 104: 13)
    - Luce, Stephen, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 104: 14)
    - Lucas, Mr. and Mrs. Paul, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 104: 15)
    - Luque, Jesus, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 104: 16)
    - McArthur, Helen Hayes, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 104: 17)
    - Macaya, Juan, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 104: 18)
    - McCahill, Charles, 1957 (Box-folder 105: 1)
    - McCampbell, David, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 105: 2)
    - McCarthy, Francis, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 105: 3)
    - McCarthy, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph, 1957 (Box-folder 105: 4)
    - McDevitt, Vincent, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - McElroy, Neil, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 105: 6)
    - McEvoy, Joseph, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 105: 7)
    - McFall, Jack, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 105: 8)
    - McGuire, John, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 105: 9)
    - McIntosh, Dempster, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 105: 10)
    - McKay, Douglas, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 105: 11)
    - Mackie, George, 1955 (Box-folder 105: 12)
    - Mackie, Helen, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 105: 13)
    - McNeil, Thomas, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 105: 14)
    - Madariaga, Juan Jose de, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 105: 15)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 105: 16)
    - Marshall, Mrs. George C., 1959 (Box-folder 105: 17)
    - Martin, Tony, 1960 (Box-folder 105: 18)
    - Mason, Anne, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 105: 19)
    - Maury, Reuben, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 105: 20)
    - Mawson, Leon, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 105: 21)
    - Maxwell, Elsa, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 105: 22)
    - May, Edwin H., Jr., 1956-1959 (Box-folder 105: 23)
    - Merchant, Livingston, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 105: 24)
    - Michel, Robert, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 105: 25)
    - Minot, William A. G., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 105: 26)
    - Montereale, Principe, undated (Box-folder 105: 27)
    - Montgomery, Robert Douglass, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - Mooberry, Henry, Jr., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 106: 2)
    - Morano, Albert, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 106: 3)
    - Moreland, Andrew, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 106: 4)
    - Morgan, John Ainsworth, 1958 (Box-folder 106: 5)
    - Morisette, R. P. Armand, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 106: 6)
    - Morris, Edgar, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 106: 7)
    - Morris, Lee, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 106: 8)
    - Morse, Harry, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 106: 9)
    - Mortensen, William, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 106: 10)
    - Morton, Thruston, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 106: 11)
    - Mott, Jordan, undated (Box-folder 106: 12)
    - Mulcahey, Leo, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 106: 13)
    - Murphy, Robert D., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 106: 14)
    - Napper, B. N., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 106: 15)
    - Nash, E. C., 1955-1957 (Box-folder 106: 16)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1956-1961 (Box-folder 106: 17)
    - O'Brien, Edmund, 1960 (Box-folder 106: 18)
    - O'Brien, John G., 1957-1959 (Box-folder 106: 19)
    - Olano, Luis de, 1960 (Box-folder 106: 20)
    - Old, Francis P., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 106: 21)
    - Orlandini, Edward, 1960 (Box-folder 106: 22)
    - Ophuls, Max, 1957 (Box-folder 106: 23)
    - Ottaviano, John, Jr., 1955-1958 (Box-folder 106: 24)
    - Oyarzabel, Antonio de, 1958 (Box-folder 106: 25)
    - Palmer, Ely Eliot, 1960 (Box-folder 106: 26)
    - Pappas, Thomas, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 106: 27)
    - Parr, Charles, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 106: 28)
    - Patterson, James, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 106: 29)
    - Paxson, Harry, 1960 (Box-folder 106: 30)
    - Pearson, Carolyn, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 106: 31)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 106: 32)
    - Pegler, Westbrook, 1958 (Box-folder 106: 33)
    - Pelaez, Dionisio, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 106: 34)
    - Pell, John H. G., 1955-1958 (Box-folder 106: 35)
    - Pell, Robert, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 106: 36)
    - Persons, Wilton, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 106: 37)
    - Peterson, Oscar, 1959 (Box-folder 106: 38)
    - Phillips, Alfred, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 107: 1)
    - Potocki, Joseph, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 107: 2)
    - Potter, Brooks, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 107: 3)
    - Pryor, Samuel, Jr., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - Purtell, William A., 1955-1958 (Box-folder 107: 5)
    - Pusta, Kaarel, 1961 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - Quilleret, Pierre, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 107: 7)
    - Quincy, Edmund, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 107: 8)
    - Quinn, Henry, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 107: 9)
    - Quinn, James, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 107: 10)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 107: 11)
    - Rainaut, Marc P., 1955-1959 (Box-folder 107: 12)
    - Raymond, Gene, 1959 (Box-folder 107: 13)
    - Reincke, Frederick, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 107: 14)
    - Reitmeyer, John, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 107: 15)
    - Reston, James, 1959 (Box-folder 107: 16)
    - Reynolds, Reginald, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 107: 17)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 107: 18)
    - Richardson, Gerard, undated (Box-folder 107: 19)
    - Richmond, Ted, 1959 (Box-folder 107: 20)
    - Riddleberger, James, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 107: 21)
    - Robb, J. Hampden, 1958 (Box-folder 107: 22)
    - Robertson, Natalie, 1959 (Box-folder 107: 23)
    - Robertson, Richard, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 107: 24)
    - Rockefeller, David, 1960 (Box-folder 107: 25)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1960 (Box-folder 107: 26)
    - Rockwell, Stuart, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 107: 27)
    - Roots, John McC., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 107: 28)
    - Rosen, Lucie, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 107: 29)
    - Routh, Robert, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 107: 30)
    - Russo, Frank, 1960 (Box-folder 107: 31)
    - Ryan, Frank, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 107: 32)
    - Sacksteder, Fred, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 108: 1)
    - Sampsell, Marshall, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 108: 2)
    - Sargent, Louise, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 3)
    - Saunders, James, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 4)
    - Savitt, Max, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 108: 5)
    - Schiavone, Mrs. Albert, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 108: 6)
    - Schwolsky, Harry, undated (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - Sears, Mason, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 108: 8)
    - Seely-Brown, Horace, Jr., 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 9)
    - Shanley, Bernard, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 108: 10)
    - Shea, Mrs. George, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 11)
    - Shinn, Allen, 1960 (Box-folder 108: 12)
    - Shuman, E. Arthur, Jr., 1958-1960 (Box-folder 108: 13)
    - Sicre, Ricardo, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 108: 14)
    - Simmons, A. L., 1958 (Box-folder 108: 15)
    - Sitnik, Zig, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 16)
    - Skelton, Mr. and Mrs. Red, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 108: 17)
    - Smedberg, William R., III, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 18)
    - Smith, Anna, 1960 (Box-folder 108: 19)
    - Smith, David S., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 108: 20)
    - Smith, Truman, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 108: 21)
    - Smith, William B., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 108: 22)
    - Snyder, Wanda, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 108: 23)
    - Sokolsky, George, 1960 (Box-folder 108: 24)
    - Speaks, Charme, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 108: 25)
    - Speiden, John, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 108: 26)
    - Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 108: 27)
    - Stalker, Hugh, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 108: 28)
    - Steele, Bernard, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 108: 29)
    - Stevens, John, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 108: 30)
    - Stilson, Germaine, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 108: 31)
    - Stratton, William G., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 108: 32)
    - Strauss, Lewis, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 108: 33)
    - Streel, Baron and Baroness de, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 108: 34)
    - Sullivan, Peter, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 109: 1-3)
    - Symington, James, 1958 (Box-folder 109: 4)
    - Tanner, Arturo, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 109: 5)
    - Taylor, Charles, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 109: 6)
    - Taylor, Henry, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 109: 7)
    - Terry, C. M., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 109: 8)
    - Thaw, Lawrence, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 109: 9)
    - Thomas, Charles, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 109: 10)
    - Thompson, Llewellyn, 1960 (Box-folder 109: 11)
    - Tierney, Mr. and Mrs., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 109: 12)
    - Tobin, Richard, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 109: 13)
    - Tomlin, Regina, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 109: 14)
    - Touche, Armand, 1961 (Box-folder 109: 15)
    - Tournelle, Guy de la, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 109: 16)
    - Towne, Charles, 1959 (Box-folder 109: 17)
    - Townsend, Natalie, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 109: 18)
    - Trohan, Walter, 1960 (Box-folder 109: 19)
    - True, David, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 109: 20)
    - Tunney, Mr. and Mrs. Gene, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 109: 21)
    - Turner, Huntington, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 109: 22)
    - Tuthill, Fred, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 109: 23)
    - Tutoli, Benedict, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 109: 24)
    - Unander, Sig, 1959 (Box-folder 110: 1)
    - Valletta, Vittorio, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 110: 2)
    - Van Allen, James, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 110: 3)
    - Volodine, George, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 110: 4)
    - Volpe, John A., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 110: 5)
    - Wadsworth, James, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - Wagner, Gerald, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - Wallace, DeWitt, 1958 (Box-folder 110: 8)
    - Ward, Stuart, 1960 (Box-folder 110: 9)
    - Waterworth, Harold, 1958 (Box-folder 110: 10)
    - Watt, Raymond, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 110: 11)
    - Welles, Benjamin, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 110: 12)
    - White, Robert J., 1956-1960 (Box-folder 110: 13)
    - Whitney, John Hay, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 110: 14)
    - Wilde, Frazar, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 110: 15)
    - Wiley, Alexander, 1957 (Box-folder 110: 16)
    - Willauer, Whiting, 1960 (Box-folder 110: 17)
    - Willems, John, 1955 (Box-folder 110: 18)
    - Williams, Frank, 1958 (Box-folder 110: 19)
    - Williams, Paul, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 110: 20)
    - Willmott, Eve, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 110: 21)
    - Wisdom, John Minor, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 110: 22)
    - Wood, John W., 1957-1958 (Box-folder 110: 23)
    - Woodbridge, Henry, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 110: 24)
    - Wright, Cobina, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 110: 25)
    - Wright, Jerauld, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 110: 26)
    - Yacopino, John, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 110: 27)
    - Yost, Charles, 1959 (Box-folder 110: 28)
    - Yudain, Bernard, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 110: 29)
    - Zeller, Fred, 1958 (Box-folder 110: 30)
    - Zellerbach, James, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 110: 31)
    - Zimmerman, Charles, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 110: 32)
    - Zubizarreta, Alejandro, 1961 (Box-folder 110: 33)
  - Office file, 1955-1961, undated
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 110: 34)
    - Memoranda (Box-folder 110: 35)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 110: 36)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 110: 37)
    - Representation expenses (Box-folder 110: 38, 111: 1-5)
    - Travel file
      - Italy, 1955 August (Box-folder 111: 6)
      - 1957
        - Valencia, June (Box-folder 111: 7)
        - Washington D.C., November (Box-folder 111: 8)
      - 1958
        - Cadiz, February (Box-folder 111: 9)
        - Belgium and France, May-June (Box-folder 111: 10)
        - Santander, August (Box-folder 111: 11)
        - Washington D.C., November (Box-folder 111: 12)
      - 1959
        - Rome, February (Box-folder 111: 13)
        - Yacht trip, June (Box-folder 111: 14)
        - Santiago, October (Box-folder 112: 1)
      - 1960
        - Washington D.C., February (Box-folder 112: 2)
        - Paris, May (Box-folder 112: 3)
        - Barcelona, May-June (Box-folder 112: 4)
        - Washington D.C., November (Box-folder 112: 5)
        - Torrenmolinos and Mancha Real, December-1961 January (Box-folder 112: 6)
      - Italy, 1961 January (Box-folder 112: 7)
    - Travel vouchers (Box-folder 112: 8-10)
  - Speeches and writings, 1955-1961
    - 1955 (Box-folder 112: 11-13, 113: 1-2)
      Includes research materials and notes.
    - 1956 (Box-folder 113: 3-6)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 113: 7-8)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 114: 1-2)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 114: 3-4)
    - 1960 (Box-folder 114: 5-7)
    - 1961 (Box-folder 115: 1)
  - Subject file, 1956-1960, undated
    - Communism (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - Connecticut (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - Diplomatic and Consular Officers, Retired (DACOR) (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - Dodd, Thomas J. (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - Dulles, John Foster (Box-folder 115: 6)
    - Espionage (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - European Economic Commission, undated (Box-folder 115: 8)
      Thorkil Kristensen, speech, typescript.
    - France (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - Franco, Francisco (Box-folder 115: 10)
    - Hungary (Box-folder 115: 11)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr.
      - Clippings (Box-folder 115: 12)
      - Speeches (Box-folder 115: 13-14)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe (Box-folder 115: 15)
    - Mallett, Ivo (Box-folder 115: 16)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 115: 17)
    - National Committee For an Adequate Overseas United States Information Program (Box-folder 116: 1)
    - National Press Club (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - Presidential inauguration, 1957 (Box-folder 116: 4)
    - Radio Free Europe, 1956 October-November (Box-folder 116: 5)
      Broadcasts to Hungary.
    - Republican Party
      - General (Box-folder 116: 6)
      - Presidential campaign, 1960 (Box-folder 116: 7-8)
    - Rogers, William P. (Box-folder 116: 9)
    - Rumania, 1958 March (Box-folder 116: 10)
      Includes Boletin Rumania (in Spanish).
    - Spain (Box-folder 116: 11, 117: 1)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (U.S.S.R.) (Box-folder 117: 2)
    - United Nations (Box-folder 117: 3)
    - United States
      - Agriculture, 1959 January 29 (Box-folder 117: 4)
        Printed report to Congress from President Dwight D. Eisenhower.
      - Defense, 1959 June 25 (Box-folder 117: 5)
        Rear Admiral H.A. Yeager, speech.
      - Department of Justice (Box-folder 117: 6)
      - Foreign relations, 1960 September 6 (Box-folder 117: 7)
        Memorandum on the "U.S. Government's Views on the Outcome of the San Jose Meeting of the American States Foreign Ministers."
      - Politics and government
        - General (Box-folder 117: 8)
        - Elections, 1958 (Box-folder 117: 9)
        - Presidential campaign, 1960 (Box-folder 117: 10)
        - Printed matter (Box-folder 117: 11)
- Interim Years (1961-1969) File, 1954-1969, 1976 (Boxes 117-186)
  Biographical material (including Lodge's 1962 and 1964 congressional election campaigns), correspondence, speeches and writings, and general subject material (including Nixon's 1968 presidential campaign).
  - Biographical file, 1961-1969, undated
    - Address lists, calling cards (Box-folder 117: 12)
    - Appointment calendars (Box-folder 118: 1)
    - Awards, decorations, and honorary degrees (Box-folder 118: 2)
    - Biographical sketches (Box-folder 118: 3)
    - Campaign, 1962
      - Candidates (Box-folder 118: 4)
      - Committees (Box-folder 118: 5-6)
        Lodge for Governor Committee and Lodge for Senator Committee.
      - Convention (Box-folder 118: 7)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 118: 8-11)
        Includes letters from Clarence Baldwin, Hamilton Eames, Robert Hill, Gordon Lamont, and Herman Levy.
      - Finances (Box-folder 118: 12)
      - Issues (Box-folder 118: 13)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 119: 1)
      - Publicity (Box-folder 119: 2)
      - Speeches (Box-folder 119: 3)
      - Travel (Box-folder 119: 4)
    - Campaign, 1964
      - Candidates (Box-folder 119: 5)
      - Committees and clubs
        - Committee to Support Moderate Republicans (Box-folder 119: 6)
        - Fair Campaign Practices Committee (Box-folder 119: 7)
        - League of Women Voters (Box-folder 119: 8)
        - Lodge for Senator Committee (Box-folder 119: 9)
        - Planning Committee (Box-folder 119: 10)
        - Veterans Committee for John Lodge (Box-folder 119: 11)
      - Convention (Box-folder 119: 12)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 119: 13-15, 120: 1-5)
        Includes letters from William Buckley, Jr., Prescott Bush, Leslie Groves, Herbert Hoover, Henry Luce, Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr., Gerald Ford and Nelson Rockefeller.
      - Endorsements (Box-folder 120: 6)
      - Ethnic groups (Box-folder 120: 7)
      - Finances (Box-folder 121: 1-2)
      - Issues (Box-folder 121: 3-4)
      - Opponent (Box-folder 121: 5-6)
      - Publicity
        - General (Box-folder 121: 7)
        - Campaign literature (Box-folder 121: 8)
        - Newsletter (Box-folder 122: 1)
        - Press releases, June-November (Box-folder 122: 2-3)
        - Radio (Box-folder 122: 4)
        - Television (Box-folder 122: 5)
        - Speeches
          - Acceptance and campaign (Box-folder 122: 6)
          - Prescott Bush speech for J.D. Lodge (Box-folder 122: 7)
        - Travel and appearances, June-October (Box-folder 122: 8-12)
      - Voter lists (Box-folder 123: 1)
    - Clippings, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 123: 2 - 125: 1)
    - Family (Box-folder 125: 2)
    - John Lodge Throughway (Box-folder 125: 3)
    - Memberships
      - General (Box-folder 125: 4)
      - Alumni associations (Box-folder 125: 5-6)
      - Chowder and Marching Club (Box-folder 125: 7)
      - Fox Club (Box-folder 125: 8)
      - France-America Society (Box-folder 125: 9)
      - Metropolitan Club (Box-folder 125: 10)
      - Navy League of the United States (Box-folder 125: 11)
      - Society of Colonial Wars (Box-folder 125: 12)
    - Miscellany (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - Oral history, Columbia University, typescript, 1967 (Box-folder 126: 2)
    - Organization of American States (Box-folder 126: 3)
    - Social functions, 1961-1969, undated (Box-folder 126: 4-13)
    - Souvenirs, programs, etc. (Box-folder 127: 1)
    - Travel
      - Israel (Box-folder 127: 2)
      - Nassau (Box-folder 127: 3)
      - Travel orders, itineraries and schedules (Box-folder 127: 4)
    - U.S. Naval Reserve
      - General
        - Career records (Box-folder 127: 5-9)
          Includes retirement records.
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 127: 10-11)
        - Correspondence Course Center (Box-folder 127: 12)
      - Active duty, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 128: 1-5)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 128: 6)
    - U.S. Navy
      - National Reserve Officers Training Corps (NROTC) Selection Committee (Box-folder 128: 7)
      - National Strategy Seminars (Box-folder 128: 8)
      - Navy League (Box-folder 128: 9)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1969
    - General
      - Undated (Box-folder 128: 10)
      - 1961 (Box-folder 129: 1-4)
      - 1962 (Box-folder 129: 5-8, 130: 1-3)
      - 1963 (Box-folder 130: 4-6)
      - 1964 (Box-folder 130: 7-9, 131: 1-2)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 131: 3-7)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 131: 8-9, 132: 1)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 132: 2-4)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 132: 5-7, 133: 1-2)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 133: 3-5)
    - Adorno, Joseph, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 133: 6)
    - Agnew, Mrs. Spiro, 1969 (Box-folder 133: 7)
    - Ainley, Mrs. Henry, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 133: 8)
    - Alabart, Manuel, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 133: 9)
    - Alba, Jaime, 1961 (Box-folder 133: 10)
    - Alcorn, H. Meade, Jr., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 133: 11)
    - Aldrich, Richard, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 133: 12)
    - Allen, Arthur, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 133: 13)
    - Allen, Craig, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 133: 14)
    - Allen, Edward, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 133: 15)
    - Alliance Francaise of Fairfield County, 1966 (Box-folder 133: 16)
    - Alphand, Herve, 1965 (Box-folder 133: 17)
    - Alsop, John, 1963 (Box-folder 133: 18)
    - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 134: 1)
    - American Bar Association, 1964 (Box-folder 134: 2)
    - American Committee for Liberation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 134: 3)
    - American Committee on Italian Migration, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 134: 4)
    - American Economic Foundation, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 134: 5)
    - American Friends of Lafayette, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 134: 6)
    - American Hungarian Studies Foundation, 1963 (Box-folder 134: 7)
    - American Legion Post, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 134: 8-9)
    - American Research Hospital - Poland, 1966 (Box-folder 134: 10)
    - American Taxpayers' Association, 1968 (Box-folder 134: 11)
    - Amoros, Salvador, undated (Box-folder 134: 12)
    - Anderson, George, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 134: 13)
    - Anderson, Neil, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 134: 14)
    - Anderson, Robert P., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 134: 15)
    - Angers, Bob, 1968 (Box-folder 134: 16)
    - Annenberg, Walter, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 134: 17)
    - Antoniazzi, John, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 134: 18)
    - Arburua, Manuel, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 134: 19)
    - Aristegui, Pedro, 1965 (Box-folder 134: 20)
    - Armstrong, Park, 1961 (Box-folder 134: 21)
    - Arnon, Michael, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 134: 22)
    - Associated Clubs Inc., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 134: 23)
    - Aznar, Manuel, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 135: 1)
    - Bacon, Virginia, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 135: 2)
    - Bailey, Consuelo, 1966 (Box-folder 135: 3)
    - Baird, Jack, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 135: 4)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm, 1968 (Box-folder 135: 5)
    - Baldwin, Herbert, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 135: 6)
    - Baldwin, Raymond, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 135: 7)
    - Balzo, Giulio del, 1968 (Box-folder 135: 8)
    - Barnes, E. Bartlett, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 135: 9)
    - Barnett, Frank, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 135: 10-12)
    - Bataille, G., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 135: 13)
    - Bay Path Jr. College, 1966 (Box-folder 135: 14)
    - Becerro de Bengoa, Ricardo, 1961 (Box-folder 135: 15)
    - Bell, J. G., 1964-1967 (Box-folder 135: 16)
    - Benton, William, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 135: 17)
    - Berk, Harry, 1966 (Box-folder 135: 18)
    - Bertran Guell, Felipe, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 135: 19)
    - Bishop, Max, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 136: 1)
    - Bliss, Robert, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 136: 2)
    - Bobich, Gica, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 136: 3)
    - Bobst, Elmer, 1969 (Box-folder 136: 4)
    - Bolton, Frances, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 136: 5)
    - Bolz, Harriett, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 136: 6)
    - Bowdin, Dina, 1962 (Box-folder 136: 7)
    - Boyd, John, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 136: 8)
    - Braden, Spruille, 1967 (Box-folder 136: 9)
    - Bradley, Kenneth, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 136: 10)
    - Bradley, O., 1969 March (Box-folder 136: 11)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 136: 12)
    - Braggiotti, George Nelson, 1961 (Box-folder 136: 13)
    - Braggiotti, Mario, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 136: 14)
    - Braggiotti, Rama, 1962 (Box-folder 136: 15)
    - Braggiotti, Sebastiano, 1964 (Box-folder 136: 16)
    - Brandeis University, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 136: 17)
    - Brennan, William H., undated (Box-folder 136: 18)
    - Brooks, J. Crawford, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 136: 19)
    - Brown, Charles, 1964 (Box-folder 136: 20)
    - Brown, John Mason, 1969 (Box-folder 136: 21)
    - Brownell, Herbert, 1968 (Box-folder 136: 22)
    - Brouilette, C. Bader, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 136: 23)
    - Bruce, David K. E., 1967 (Box-folder 136: 24)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1961-1967 (Box-folder 136: 25)
    - Burke, Arleigh, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 136: 26)
    - Bush, Prescott, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 136: 27)
    - Bushell, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 136: 28)
    - Byington, Homer, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 137: 1)
    - Byrnes, John W., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 137: 2)
    - Cabot, John M., 1965 (Box-folder 137: 3)
    - Calvo-Sotelo, Joaquin, 1968 (Box-folder 137: 4)
    - Carroll-Abbing, John, 1962 (Box-folder 137: 5)
    - Carson, Mrs. George, 1963 (Box-folder 137: 6)
    - Case, Clifford, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 137: 7)
    - Casey, John T., 1961-1967 (Box-folder 137: 8)
    - Casey, William J., 1966 (Box-folder 137: 9)
      Includes materials on Vietnam.